Dreaded by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his trials, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
woooo
Woa a
Woa
It felt like I'd stop solving
I want to believe I'll be happy
Halfway, dost a absorbs
I want such a how it experiencing
We should practice and enjoy it
Every time it makes
Brilliant in blue
Get a monkey cry and fight
だから待って 待って 待って 待って
置いてかないでてよ
今すぐ fly away
戦むよ try again
だから待って 待って 待って
同じ場所にいたいよ
霞のに大体胸の痛みが
君に話したい僕の気持ちが
本当のことね
ベイピッパーライ
僕の気持ちができるよ
anyway Goldie Guts wasn't the only night
that started behaving like a lunatic
out of nowhere
Marks and the doctor did too
even the prickly princess is different
no way Captain Charlotte
obviously a whole lot of crazy stuff went down
while you were in here taking a nap
you do know I almost died right
you could say that
I am saying that
I was worried
oh sure I can tell
no I'm serious
I couldn't sleep a wink for days
we're lucky they didn't take control of you too
hey wait I wonder if that's what happened to Longris
probably
that ominous mana I felt
the way he tried to kill me with no hesitation
hey Fenril
you ready
yes sir
Longris
I'll stop you this time
I swear I will
flame magic
explosive
gutter shot
not half bad
for a delinquent
why are you out here Vanessa
I just got done visiting Fenril
and I figured you would be crying your eyes out from loneliness
so I stopped by to make you feel better
crying?
me?
you're right
and who said you could sit on my crazy cyclone huh?
look
just don't interrupt my training
Asta, Luck and Noelle are out there destroying the midnight sun with the royal knights right now
most likely
I outrank those three
so I'll be an embarrassment to them if I'm not as good as they are
that's why
I have to become stronger
I promise you I'll come back alive okay?
go ahead without me
what's wrong with you tell me
tell me
please can't you see you're nothing but strangers to us now
no
I told you it's pointless
stop screaming or we'll silence you ourselves
lavao
i and also
love
hold mass
what's wrong with you
you should just be running
and get out of the Renaissance
Laos, listen to me
you can't do this
her
what's wrong with you
your
you can't do this
and—
and how
how
I'm begging you, stop it!
We're all magic knights, don't you remember that?
This body, it's responding to his words.
You fool!
Regardless of what we were in the past,
our grudge is far deeper than any bond we shared!
Easy. Don't go overboard, or you'll wind up dead.
What a pain.
Though, I guess as soon as we get the grimoire and the swords,
you won't be of any more use to us.
Doesn't look like you're planning to give up.
Well, if you're set on dying to protect your royal pal,
by all means, have at it.
Asta, no!
Not yet.
Huh?
I'm not dying! Not yet!
I made a promise to my friend that I would get out of this place alive!
I won't let teammates kill each other!
I'll survive!
I'll get through this!
And one day...
I'll become the Wizard King!
You showed me it was possible.
Gave me hope.
That even though we're poor orphans,
commoners,
we can still make something of ourselves in this world.
And to prove that...
to make Sister Lily and everybody else happy.
We'll fight to see who will be the Wizard King!
Whatever it takes!
That was quite an impressive speech
coming from someone who's too weak to move his body.
We've heard enough.
This is where you die.
Human!
Save your breath.
Asta.
The next Wizard King...
is me.
You know...
Wait! I'm confused!
Is that you or not?
I mean, you knew my name, so...
Yeah, it's me.
What? Are you sure?
You got pointy ears and stuff!
So what if I do?
Who cares?
It's just...
You're acting normal!
I'm here too!
And look!
We even have matching ears now!
Belle, please stop talking.
Yeah, we're kinda in the middle of something here.
That's so rude!
Forget the shorty!
Why don't you start complimenting me
on my cuteness or something?
Who are you calling shorty?
At least I'm more than three inches tall!
Five inches!
Quiet, both of you.
I'm glad they're not possessed.
But I do wish they'd get me down from here already.
I'm the same me.
You got a problem with that?
No way!
It's great!
Oh, so you two are buddies again!
I told you, pay attention to me or I'll...
You're awakened!
It's good to have you on our side.
Come stand over here.
Excuse me?
I was talking!
Thank you!
Judging by that mana,
the reincarnation must have been a success.
He's not quite ready, though.
And even with his swords and grimoire right in front of him,
Licht isn't responding at all.
Maybe it's because he just used the highest order of forbidden magic
to bring his elven friends back from the dead.
We're definitely going to need some more time.
For Licht,
and for you.
I'm not sure exactly what's happening,
but I can sense that there are different souls moving within their bodies.
Klaus and Hammond, as we know them,
are lying dormant somewhere on the inside.
Oh, really?
So how are we going to bring them back?
Um, thank you so much for rescuing me, Asta.
And inside my body.
What's up?
Still,
I am Yuno,
one of the magic knights of the Clover Kingdom.
And no one else!
This is a shame.
That human vessel is awfully stubborn.
It's clear now.
He hasn't fully awakened.
The humans have tainted him.
Very well.
We'll slay those vermin behind you
and exorcise you from that body!
What?
Those bodies belong to my squadmates.
Leave them now or I will force you out!
Well, if this is the way you want to behave...
You've left us no choice!
Whoa!
We're making the room shake just by glaring at us!
Not good!
I know I can't fix this,
but I can stun and capture them.
I'll stop them.
You and Mimosa stand back.
Yeah, right!
I want in on this too!
Save some fun for me!
Yuno doesn't need you, Shorty.
You've got me with him!
Mimosa!
Could you give us a little extra room to work here?
Okay!
With new developments and improved grimoires,
magic is significantly more refined than it was during our time.
I agree.
Combo magic!
Le Chateau de Ber!
You're finished!
That is a tough-looking spell!
You're not scared, right?
Their power is outrageous.
I can't protect us both this time.
Good luck!
Here we go!
Onward!
Le Chateau de Ber!
Run!
It's over!
Ah!
Wow, that was amazing, you two!
The anti-magic brat's enough of a pain.
But now this one gets the magic boost from reincarnation,
even though he's not completely awakened yet?
Licked.
He should be out of power.
How's he able to make things levitate?
The mana's extremely dense.
This is impossible!
Now we have to defeat their leader?
What's with the sword?
Nero?
Cut that out!
It really hurts!
Oh, now is that the time!
His key...
That sword's got massive power.
Uh-oh.
I can't stay in this form much longer.
Come on, just a little more.
Asta, careful, all right?
Yeah, I know that.
He's fast.
No, it's more like he's melted into the air.
I can't read his key now.
Why can't I pick up his mana?
Did he somehow become one with the natural mana around him?
O Facebook are negative.
Arsa!
Let's go.
May he will save your you.
Magic! Live attack!
Please don't miss.
Where did all that confidence go?
Hasta, look out!
He's casting fast movement. Now what?
This is where we push past our limits!
That's your big plan?
Wingspirit magic!
Spirit Sword!
Enjoy my magic torch!
That's just one of the fun little perks that comes with the original Demon Dweller Sword.
Ugh!
This guy is strong. And what the heck did he do to my sword? I don't know what's going on anymore. I hate this. Come on, buddy. You can't give out on me. Not now!
That run should be reaching his limit any second. I'm pretty worn out myself. But hey, good job getting this far.
Austin!
Austin! You know... I can't heal them right now. My magic is...
I can't find an opening. Time to change my approach.
You know... I can't heal them right now.
My magic is...
I can't find an opening.
Time to change my approach.
Not yet.
Not yet!
I'm surprised he can handle attacks that fast.
Nice moves.
Not yet!
Alright.
My turn!
Monozone!
That's what that fire chick used.
Watch out!
Spirit Guard!
Look at that!
He's only part way through the reincarnation process
and he's still managed to catch him off guard.
Well, I guess he and Lyft are...
Wait!
I thought he couldn't move.
This is it.
Austin's pushing past his limits.
I'm not done yet!
The timing is perfect, but they planned it that way.
Who are these two?
You're not killing Yunu!
Trust either!
He's my rival!
RIVAL!
He blocked it with that sword?
Yes.
He's condensing a huge amount of magic.
Is this Yunu's spell?
Grr.
What're you doing?
Yau!
I am trying not to kill yவos!
Huh?!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaah!
I am trying not to kill him now!
Tori has been zeathed.
They decide for him his wife who filed.
WAAAAAAAA stretching!
The threat is excellent.
That's very slick!
Is this Yunu's spell?
OK, it's done!
I don't know.
I don't need no money.
I don't need no魔力はいらない。
自力で挑んだミラクル起きること願い。
微力ながら1ミリずっとビリビリ切り込んでく。
世界を巻き込んでく。
My disability is my ability.
逆にそれが俺のエネルギー。
どうしても自らを見失って嫌いになって負けそうになったら Just cry out loud。
傷つく音に、傷つく音に。
勝ち向かう勇気へと導いてく our treasure.
裏切らないのは最高に there is love.
かざしたちがい光が生きる treasure.
ご視聴ありがとうございました。